I'm Peppa Pig. [snorts]
-This is my little brother, George.
-[snorts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[Mommy Pig snorts]
And this is Daddy Pig.
-[Daddy Pig snorts]
-[all laugh]
Peppa Pig. [snorts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are watching sport on television.
It's a long jump. It's a new world record.
[crowd on TV] Hooray!
[snorts] Mommy, what's a world record?
It means you're best
in the world at something.
Then you are a champion
and your name goes in a book.
There are champions for running,
jumping, swimming...
I wish you were in the book, Daddy.
-I am in the book.
-No.
Yes, Daddy Pig is champion puddle jumper.
[Peppa & George] Wow.
[Daddy Pig] No one has beaten me yet.
I don't think they ever will.
The next event is the puddle jump.
[crowd cheering on TV]
That was a very big splash.
In fact, I think...
Yes, it's a new world record.
Oh.
[snorts] Daddy,
you're not the champion anymore.
Everyone will be sad.
Ho, ho.
I'm sure they've got more important things
to worry about, Peppa.
[doorbell rings]
Daddy Pig, you lost the world record.
-Everybody wants you to be champion again.
-It's important.
Really?
[all] Yes.
Okay, I'll do it. Tomorrow.
[crowd] Hooray!
But I'll have to train myself
to jump in muddy puddles again.
Everyone knows how
to jump in muddy puddles, Daddy.
Ah, but not everyone is a champion, Peppa.
Daddy Pig is the master.
Daddy, are you going
to practice jumping up and down?
No, Peppa.
I must be at one with the puddle.
What?
To jump in a puddle,
I must think like a puddle.
-Do you need to do running?
-No.
Do you need to do press-ups?
No.
I need to sleep. And dream about puddles.
[rooster crows]
[narrator] It is the day
of the big puddle jump.
Daddy Pig is wearing
his puddle-jumping costume.
I can't find my golden boots.
I gave those old boots to Grandpa,
for gardening.
My lucky golden boots?
To be used as gardening boots?
-You've got other ones.
-It's not the same.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Grandpa,
remember those old boots I gave you?
Uh... yes.
Daddy needs them back urgently.
You have been looking after them?
Um, they have been watered.
[narrator] Grandpa Pig is growing tomatoes
in Daddy's lucky boots.
[snorts] We need them
for the puddle jump today.
Right-o. I'll meet you there.
[all chattering]
[narrator] Everyone has come
to watch Daddy Pig's puddle jump.
Please, welcome your friend and mine,
Mr. Potato.
[crowd] Hooray!
Good luck, Daddy Pig.
Oh, but where are your lucky boots?
Ah. Here they are.
Thank you, Grandpa Pig.
[sniffs] I can smell tomatoes.
And now for Daddy Pig's puddle jump.
[narrator] Daddy Pig is thinking.
Ready. Steady.
Go.
I must become one with the puddle.
I must be the puddle.
[yells]
The puddle has gone.
[giggles] The puddle has gone
over all of us.
[narrator] Daddy Pig has become one
with the puddle.
Everyone has become one with the puddle.
It's a new world record.
[crowd] Hooray!
[snorts] Champion Daddy Pig.
And who is this?
I'm Peppa Pig.
One day,
I will be the champion puddle jumper.
I've been training her.
Ah, to be trained by the master.
What have you learned?
Uh... if you jump in muddy puddles,
you must wear your boots.
[crowd laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny day,
and Suzy Sheep has come
to play with Peppa.
[snorts] Hello, Suzy.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
[narrator] Peppa and Suzy
are best friends.
Guess what happened to me yesterday.
[snorts] Yesterday I went to the duck pond
and I saw Mrs. Duck.
Well, yesterday--
Then I went to the supermarket with Mommy.
We bought bread, carrots and...
What's wrong?
You talk too much.
You go, "Blah, blah, blah."
Just like that, "Blah, blah, blah."
Mummy, Suzy said I talk too much.
Well, you are a bit of a chatterbox,
Peppa.
Chatterbox. That's right.
Chatterbox here. Chatterbox there.
Chatter, chatter, chatter.
You never stop talking.
[snorts] I can easily stop talking
if I want to.
No, you can't.
Yes, I can.
You can't.
I can.
That's it.
I'm never going to talk again.
[bell dings]
Hello, Suzy. Hello, Peppa.
[bleats] Hello, Zoë. You look nice today.
Thank you, Suzy. This is my new dress.
Why are you not talking, Peppa?
Yes. Why are you not talking, Peppa?
[sighs] This is a silly game.
What game are you playing?
Suzy said I was a chatterbox
and I could never be quiet.
You're not being very quiet now,
are you? [laughs]
Right. I'm not going to talk ever again.
Starting now.
[bell dings]
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Danny.
What's the matter with Peppa?
She's not talking.
Oh. Who wants a grape?
Me, please.
[grunts]
You can't nod your head. That's cheating.
And you can't blink.
[horn honks]
Hello, everyone.
[all] Hello, Pedro.
What's the matter with Peppa?
She's never going to talk ever again.
Why?
Because she talks too much.
I do not talk too much.
Anyway, you're always walking like this:
"Oh, look at me. I'm Suzy Sheep."
See what I mean?
And you say this:
Micky macky boo bah boo.
That's nothing like me.
It is a bit like you, Suzy.
You're just as noisy as me. [snorts]
I can be quiet.
It's not easy.
It's not that hard, Peppa.
Okay. You do it, then.
Let's all do it.
We can show my mommy.
[all giggling]
Mommy, we're all going to be quiet.
Very quiet.
So quiet you can drop something
on the floor and hear it.
Quiet as a mouse.
[all giggle]
But you're not being quiet at all.
You're all being very noisy.
We can be quiet whenever we want.
Start being quiet on the count of three.
-One, two--
-I'm not ready.
Okay, now.
On your marks.
-Ready...
-Get set.
Three.
[horn honks]
Hello. [snorts] I'm home.
Oh. I thought the house was empty.
Peppa and her friends are playing
at being quiet.
[snorts] It's not playing.
It's very hard work.
[children] Oh, Peppa.
[narrator] Peppa cannot stop herself
from talking.
Oh, Daddy.
I think I might be a chatterbox.
That's not such a bad thing, Peppa.
It's good to talk.
In fact,
I think you're an expert at talking.
That's right. [snorts]
I am an expert at talking.
[bleats] I'm an expert at talking, too.
No, you're not. I'm the chatterbox.
I'm more of a chatterbox than you.
Ho, ho.
You two are just the same.
Yes, we are.
-That's why we are best friends.
-Chatter, chatter...
[narrator] Peppa loves talking.
Suzy loves talking.
Everybody loves talking.
[all] Chatter...
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny day.
Peppa is playing with her friends.
[snorts] It's Freddy Fox.
[barks] Hello, everyone.
-[all] Hello, Freddy.
-[Freddy barks]
Come on, let's cycle to the big hill.
[all cheer, then giggle]
Good morning, Mr. Fox.
It's afternoon, Mr. Pig.
Afternoon? Already?
My watch must have stopped.
My shop sells watches and clocks.
Let me see what I've got in the van.
One grandfather clock.
It's a bit big.
Good, isn't it?
It actually comes in a set of three.
Oh.
[bells dinging]
[snorts] Who's got the loudest bell?
I haven't got a bell.
Oh.
But my dad will have one
in the back of his van.
-Three clocks are much better than one.
-Dad?
Have you got a bicycle bell, please?
How many do you want, son?
I only want one.
I do them in boxes of two.
[narrator] Freddy Fox
now has two bicycle bells.
[bells dinging]
Brilliant.
Thanks, Dad.
[bells dinging]
Dad gave me two bells.
[all] Wow.
What else has your dad got in his van?
He's got everything.
[all] Ooh.
[snorts] What shall we play now?
Let's have a bicycle race.
With a big shiny cup for the winner.
But where can we get a cup?
Yes, where can we get a cup?
I'll see what I can do.
The best thing about having
your own cement mixer is--
Dad, have you got a big shiny winner's cup
for our bicycle race, please?
How important a race is it?
It's very important.
Will this do?
Wow, thanks, Dad. It's gold.
Yes. It's plastic gold.
[Freddy & Daddy Pig] Ooh.
[bells dinging]
One winner's cup.
It's made of plastic gold.
[all] Wow.
Your daddy's van
really has got everything.
Yep.
[neighs] Let's race to Peppa's house.
Ready. Steady. Go.
[bells dinging & children giggling]
Press this button and it just disappears.
[Mommy Pig & Daddy Pig] Ooh.
[Mommy Pig & Daddy Pig] Ah!
And if you push this button,
you can play CDs.
[rock music playing over speakers]
[all giggling]
[narrator] The friends have all finished
together.
-Everyone's a winner.
-[children giggling]
But we've only got one cup.
My van has a winner's cup for everyone.
[both] Hooray!
Mr. Fox, is there anything
you don't have in your van?
Try me.
Have you got a banjo?
Four- or five-string?
[bleats] You won't have a tree
in your van.
-[children giggle]
-Apple or pear?
[woofs] I bet you haven't got a rocket
in there.
Boxes of five.
What about a chicken?
One chicken.
[chicken clucks]
[both giggle]
Mr. Fox's van is magic.
It's a super van.
Yes, it is. Come on, Freddy.
We'd better get home.
-Goodbye, everyone.
-Bye.
[all] Bye.
-Have you got a bouncy castle?
-Yep.
-A garden shed?
-Yep. I've got everything.
[engine stutters]
Oh, I've got no petrol.
[narrator] Mr. Fox has everything
in his van, except petrol.
Hmm. I need to get to the petrol station.
I would tow you,
but I haven't got a towrope.
Oh, I've got plenty of them.
I do them in packs of five.
Can we come along, too?
[chuckles] Why not?
[children giggling]
[narrator] Daddy Pig is towing
Mr. Fox's van to the petrol station.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are on their way to visit Cousin Chloé.
I love playing with big Cousin Chloé.
[George snorts, then both giggle]
-[snorts] Chloé! Chloé!
-Chloé! Chloé!
-Oh. Chloé.
-Hi there.
These are my friends
Simon Squirrel and Belinda Bear.
You can call me Si. It's short for Simon.
And I'm Bee. It's short for Belinda.
[snorts] I'm Peppa.
-We'll call you Peh.
-Oh.
And this is George.
-We'll call you Ger.
-Oh.
You didn't tell us you had baby cousins,
Chloé.
[snorts] I'm not a baby.
But you're both little.
I'm a big girl.
George is little.
Uh... why don't we all play a game?
-[snorts] Yes. Let's play hide-and-seek.
-[snorts]
We don't play baby games anymore.
We're almost grown up.
[snorts] What about the yes-no game?
What's the yes-no game?
I ask things and you answer.
What makes that a game?
You mustn't say yes or no.
Too easy.
-Do you want to play, then?
-Yes.
Aha! You said yes.
[Peppa & George giggle]
That's not fair. I wasn't ready.
Bee? Are you ready?
Yes.
Aha! I win again. [giggling]
[narrator] Peppa is very good
at playing the yes-no game.
Can I ask the questions?
Of course.
You don't mind me
asking you the questions?
I don't mind.
Am I ever going to make you say yes or no?
I don't think so.
Oh, I give up.
How do you always win?
Easy. I just don't say yes or no.
Ah! I win. You said yes and no.
[all laugh]
That was fun.
Let's play another game.
Have you ever played sardines?
What's that?
Someone hides and we all try to find them.
That sounds like hide-and-seek.
But when you find them, you keep quiet
and hide in the same space.
Until everyone is hiding there.
Like sardines in a tin.
All right. Let's try it.
-[George snorts]
-George, you hide first.
[George giggles]
[all] One, two, three...
[narrator] George is looking
for somewhere to hide.
[all] ...nine, ten.
Ready or not, here we come.
-[George giggles]
-[Peppa snorts]
George, I can see your wiggly tail.
[giggles]
[narrator] Peppa is hiding with George.
[Peppa whispering] Move over, George.
Found you.
[narrator] Now Chloé must squeeze in
with Peppa and George.
-[Peppa giggles]
-[Chloé] Move up.
There you all are.
[narrator] Now Belinda Bear
must squeeze in, too.
-[Belinda] Budge up.
-[Peppa snorts]
We're like sardines in a tin. [giggles]
Where's everyone gone?
[all] Surprise!
[Simon yells]
[all laugh]
Can we stop running around now?
Yeah, let's just chill out.
Chill out? What's that?
We just sit around and talk about stuff.
[snorts] I like talking. Blah, blah, blah.
Let's talk about music.
I dig blues music.
Um... I like reds music.
I like greens music.
We don't like children's music.
[older children] No, no, no.
What music are you into?
I like this. It's very grown-up.
♪ Heads, shoulders, knees and toes
Knees and toes ♪
♪ And eyes and ears and mouth and nose ♪
♪ Heads, shoulders, knees and toes
Knees and toes ♪
♪ Heads, shoulders, knees and toes... ♪
[snorts] Peppa. George.
It's time to go home now.
-[music stops]
-[children] Aw.
You will see Chloé again soon.
I'm coming to your house next week, Peppa.
[both] Can we come along, too?
You can come,
but we will be playing games.
We like playing games
with Peppa and George.
[piglets] Hooray!
[narrator] You can still have fun
playing games,
even when you're almost grown up.
♪ Heads, shoulders, knees and toes
Knees and toes ♪
♪ And eyes and ears and mouth and nose ♪
♪ Heads, shoulders, knees and toes
Knees and toes ♪